It's a business doing pleasure.
Spread is a comedy, romance film directed by David Mackenzie.
A gigolo must contend with the prospect that he has found true love.
Nikki, played by Ashton Kutcher.
Samantha, played by Anne Heche.
Heather, played by Margarita Levieva.
Harry, played by Sebastian Stan.
Eva, played by Ashley Johnson.
Christina, played by Sonia Rockwell.
Spread is a 2009 American sex comedy film directed by David
Mackenzie and starring Ashton Kutcher and Anne Heche.
The film premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 17, 2009, and was released
theatrically in the United States by Anchor Bay Films on August 14, 2009.
The film explores themes of seduction, gigolo, callboy, womanizer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.